<resources>
    <!-- Login -->
    <string name="app_name">Daily Health</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="action_register">Register</string>
    <string name="action_skip">Skip</string>

    <!-- Register -->
    <!-- Intro -->
    <string name="register_title">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="register_username">Username</string>
    <string name="register_email">Email</string>
    <string name="register_password">Password</string>
    <string name="register_tandc">By signing up you agree to our terms and conditions, as well as our privacy policy</string>
    <!-- Page 1 -->
    <string name="register_1of4">1 of 4</string>
    <string name="register_page1_t">Male or Female?</string>
    <string name="register_page1_s">Men and women have different requirements when it comes to health</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <!-- Page 2 -->
    <string name="register_2of4">2 of 4</string>
    <string name="register_page2_t">How old are you?</string>
    <string name="register_page2_s">Different age ranges have different health goals</string>
    <!-- Page 3 -->
    <string name="register_3of4">3 of 4</string>
    <string name="register_page3_t">How much do you weigh?</string>
    <string name="register_page3_s">This is used to set up recommendations for you</string>
    <!-- Page 4 -->
    <string name="register_4of4">4 of 4</string>
    <string name="register_page4_t">How tall are you?</string>
    <string name="register_page4_s">This is used to set up recommendations for you</string>
    <string name="register_finish">Finish</string>

    <!-- Home Page -->
    <string name="home_page">Home Page</string>
    <string name="disease_intro">Disease Introduction</string>
    <string name="first_aid">First Aid</string>
    <string name="measurement">Measurement</string>
    <string name="health_record">Your Health Record</string>
    <string name="appointment">Make An Appointment</string>
    <string name="direct_support">Ask For Direct Support</string>
    <string name="log_out">Sign Out</string>

    <!-- Disease Intro -->
    <string name="library">LIBRARY</string>
    <string name="asthma">Asthma</string>
    <string name="diabetes">Diabetes</string>
    <string name="back_arrow">Back Arrow</string>

    <!-- Intro: Asthma -->
    <string name="introduction_asthma">Introduction: Asthma</string>
    <string name="what_is_asthma_title">What is Asthma?</string>
    <string name="what_is_asthma">Asthma is a condition in which your airways narrow and swell and produce extra mucus. This can make breathing difficult and trigger coughing, wheezing and shortness of breath.\n
        \nFor some people, asthma is a minor nuisance. For others, it can be a major problem that interferes with daily activities and may lead to a life-threatening asthma attack.\n
        \nAsthma can\'t be cured, but its symptoms can be controlled. Because asthma often changes over time, it\'s important that you work with your doctor to track your signs and symptoms and adjust treatment as needed.
    </string>
    <string name="symptoms_title">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="symptoms_asthma"><b>Asthma signs and symptoms include:</b>\n
        \n\t-Shortness of breath
        \n\t-Chest tightness or pain
        \n\t-Trouble sleeping caused by shortness of breath, coughing or wheezing
        \n\t-A whistling or wheezing sound when exhaling (wheezing is a common sign of asthma in children)
        \n\t-Coughing or wheezing attacks that are worsened by a respiratory virus, such as a cold or the flu&#xA;
        \n<b>Signs that your asthma is probably worsening include:</b>\n
        \n\t-Asthma signs and symptoms that are more frequent and bothersome
        \n\t-Increasing difficulty breathing (measurable with a peak flow meter, a device used to check how well your lungs are working)
        \n\t-The need to use a quick-relief inhaler more often\n
        \n<b>For some people, asthma signs and symptoms flare up in certain situations:</b>\n
        \n\t-Exercise-induced asthma, which may be worse when the air is cold and dry
        \n\t-Occupational asthma, triggered by workplace irritants such as chemical fumes, gases or dust
	    \n\t-Allergy-induced asthma, triggered by airborne substances, such as pollen, mold spores, cockroach waste or particles of skin and dried saliva shed by pets (pet dander)
    </string>

    <!-- Intro: Diabetes -->
    <string name="introduction_diabetes">Introduction: Diabetes</string>
    <string name="what_is_diabetes_title">What is Diabetes?</string>
    <string name="what_is_diabetes">Type I diabetes: Also known as juvenile diabetes, this type occurs when the body fails to produce insulin. People with type I diabetes are insulin-dependent, which means they must take artificial insulin daily to stay alive.\n
        \nType 2 diabetes: Type 2 diabetes affects the way the body uses insulin. While the body still makes insulin, unlike in type I, the cells in the body do not respond to it as effectively as they once did. This is the most common type of diabetes, according to the National Institute of Diabetes and Digestive and Kidney Diseases, and it has strong links with obesity.\n
        \nGestational diabetes: This type occurs in women during pregnancy when the body can become less sensitive to insulin. Gestational diabetes does not occur in all women and usually resolves after giving birth.
    </string>
    <string name="symptoms_diabetes"><b>There are diabetes warning signs and symptoms that both women and men have in common, for example:</b>\n
        \n\t-Excessive thirst and hunger
        \n\t-Frequent urination (from urinary tract infections or kidney problems)
        \n\t-Weight loss or gain
        \n\t-Fatigue
        \n\t-Irritability
        \n\t-Blurred vision
        \n\t-Slow-healing wounds
        \n\t-Nausea
        \n\t-Skin infections
        \n\t-Darkening of skin in areas of body creases (acanthosis nigricans)
        \n\t-Breath odor that is fruity, sweet, or an acetone odor
        \n\t-Tingling or numbness in the hands or feet
    </string>

    <!-- First Aid: Asthma -->
    <string name="first_aid_rescue_info">Rescue Information</string>
    <string name="how_to_prevent_title">How to prevent?</string>
    <string name="first_aid_asthma">While there\'s no way to prevent asthma, by working together, you and your doctor can design a step-by-step plan for living with your condition and preventing asthma attacks.\n
        \nFollow your asthma action plan. With your doctor and health care team, write a detailed plan for taking medications and managing an asthma attack. Then be sure to follow your plan.\n
        \nAsthma is an ongoing condition that needs regular monitoring and treatment. Taking control of your treatment can make you feel more in control of your life in general.\n
        \nGet vaccinated for influenza and pneumonia. Staying current with vaccinations can prevent flu and pneumonia from triggering asthma flare-ups.\n
        \nIdentify and avoid asthma triggers. A number of outdoor allergens and irritants — ranging from pollen and mold to cold air and air pollution — can trigger asthma attacks. Find out what causes or worsens your asthma, and take steps to avoid those triggers.\n
        \nMonitor your breathing. You may learn to recognize warning signs of an impending attack, such as slight coughing, wheezing or shortness of breath. But because your lung function may decrease before you notice any signs or symptoms, regularly measure and record your peak airflow with a home peak flow meter.\n
        \nIdentify and treat attacks early. If you act quickly, you\'re less likely to have a severe attack. You also won\'t need as much medication to control your symptoms.When your peak flow measurements decrease and alert you to an oncoming attack, take your medication as instructed and immediately stop any activity that may have triggered the attack. If your symptoms don\'t improve, get medical help as directed in your action plan.\n
        \nTake your medication as prescribed. Just because your asthma seems to be improving, don\'t change anything without first talking to your doctor. It\'s a good idea to bring your medications with you to each doctor visit, so your doctor can double-check that you\'re using your medications correctly and taking the right dose.\n
        \nPay attention to increasing quick-relief inhaler use. If you find yourself relying on your quick-relief inhaler, such as albuterol, your asthma isn\'t under control. See your doctor about adjusting your treatment.\n
    </string>

    <!-- First Aid: Diabetes -->
    <string name="first_aid_diabetes">Check your risk of diabetes. Take the Life! risk assessment test and learn more about your risk of developing type 2 diabetes. A 12+ score indicates that you are at high risk and may be eligible for the Life! program - a free Victorian lifestyle modification program that helps you reduce your risk of type 2 diabetes and cardiovascular disease, or call 13 RISK (13 7475).\n
        \nManage your weight. Excess body fat, particularly if stored around the abdomen, can increase the body\’s resistance to the hormone insulin. This can lead to type 2 diabetes.\n
        \nExercise regularly. Moderate physical activity on most days of the week helps manage weight, reduce blood glucose levels and may also improve blood pressure and cholesterol.\n
        \nEat a balanced, healthy diet. Reduce the amount of fat in your diet, especially saturated and trans fats. Eat more fruit, vegetables and high-fibre foods. Cut back on salt.\n
        \nLimit takeaway and processed foods. \‘Convenience meals\’ are usually high in salt, fat and kilojoules. It\’s best to cook for yourself using fresh ingredients whenever possible.\n
        \nLimit your alcohol intake. Too much alcohol can lead to weight gain and may increase your blood pressure and triglyceride levels. Men should have no more than two standard drinks a day and women should have no more than one.\n
        \nQuit smoking. Smokers are twice as likely to develop diabetes as non-smokers.\n
        \nControl your blood pressure. Most people can do this with regular exercise, a balanced diet and by keeping a healthy weight. In some cases, you might need medication prescribed by your doctor.\n
        \nReduce your risk of cardiovascular disease. Diabetes and cardiovascular disease have many risk factors in common, including obesity and physical inactivity.\n
        \nSee your doctor for regular check-ups. As you get older, it\’s a good idea to regularly check your blood glucose, blood pressure and blood cholesterol levels.
    </string>

    <!-- Measurement -->
    <string name="measurement_page_title">Want Our Advice?</string>
    <string name="measurement_page_subtitle">We would like to ask a few questions about your asthma condition to help make a preliminary assessment of your condition.
        \nNone of your information will be saved throughout this process, to protect your privacy</string>
    <string name="measurement_page_button1">Let\'s Do It</string>
    <string name="measurement_page_button2">Do It Later</string>
    <string name="next_stage_button">GO ON</string>
    <!-- Stage 1 -->
    <string name="stage1_7">1 of 7</string>
    <string name="measure_peak_flow_q">What is your measured peak flow?</string>
    <string name="measure_peak_flow_s">Try do this while you\'re standing, and taking the best of 3 tries</string>
    <!-- Stage 2 -->
    <string name="stage2_7">2 of 7</string>
    <string name="predicted_peak_flow_q">What is your predicted peak flow?</string>
    <string name="predicted_peak_flow_s">If you do not know or have a predicted peak flow, put \'0\' and we will calculate a general one for you</string>
    <!-- Stage 3 -->
    <string name="stage3_7">3 of 7</string>
    <string name="sentence_formation_q">How well can you form sentences?</string>
    <string name="option">Option</string>
    <string name="sentence_formation_opt1">Full Sentences</string>
    <string name="sentence_formation_opt1_s">I can speak fluently</string>
    <string name="sentence_formation_opt2">Short Sentences</string>
    <string name="sentence_formation_opt2_s">I can only get out short sentences</string>
    <string name="sentence_formation_opt3">Words Only</string>
    <string name="sentence_formation_opt3_s">I can only get out single words</string>
    <string name="sentence_formation_opt4">Can\'t Speak</string>
    <string name="sentence_formation_opt4_s">I find it very difficult to speak at all</string>
    <!-- Stage 4 -->
    <string name="stage4_7">4 of 7</string>
    <string name="respiratory_rate_q">What is your current respiration rate?</string>
    <string name="respiratory_rate_s">Count how many times your chest raises in a minute, while you\'re breathing normally</string>
    <!-- Stage 5 -->
    <string name="stage5_7">5 of 7</string>
    <string name="respiratory_effort_q">How easy is it to breathe?</string>
    <string name="respiratory_effort_opt1">Normal</string>
    <string name="respiratory_effort_opt1_s">It takes me no extra effort to breath</string>
    <string name="respiratory_effort_opt2">Hard</string>
    <string name="respiratory_effort_opt2_s">It takes me a little bit extra effort to breath</string>
    <string name="respiratory_effort_opt3">Difficult</string>
    <string name="respiratory_effort_opt3_s">It takes me a lot extra effort to breath</string>
    <string name="respiratory_effort_opt4">Challenging</string>
    <string name="respiratory_effort_opt4_s">I find it extremely hard to breath</string>
    <!-- Stage 6 -->
    <string name="stage6_7">6 of 7</string>
    <string name="heart_rate_q">What is your heart rate?</string>
    <string name="heart_rate_s">Find your pulse, then count how many beats there are in 15 seconds and multiply that by 4</string>
    <!-- Stage 7 -->
    <string name="stage7_7">7 of 7</string>
    <string name="exhaustion_q">What level of exhaustion are you experiencing?</string>
    <string name="exhaustion_opt1">None</string>
    <string name="exhaustion_opt1_s">+</string>
    <string name="exhaustion_opt2">Tired Sometimes</string>
    <string name="exhaustion_opt2_s">++</string>
    <string name="exhaustion_opt3">Tired Often</string>
    <string name="exhaustion_opt3_s">+++</string>
    <string name="exhaustion_opt4">Exhausted</string>
    <string name="exhaustion_opt4_s">++++</string>
    <!-- Results -->
    <string name="results">Your Results</string>
    <string name="severity_button1">Mild</string>
    <string name="severity_button2">Moderate</string>
    <string name="severity_button3">Severe</string>
    <string name="severity_button4">Emergency</string>
    <string name="severity_mild"><b>Your symptoms appear to be mild</b>\n
        \nWe suggest that you use a spacer, if one can be used with your preventer inhaler.
        \nCarry your reliever at all times.\n
        \n<b>Your asthma is under control when:</b>\n
        \n\t-You don’t have asthma symptoms most days (wheeze, tight chest, a cough or feeling breathless)
        \n\t-You have no cough or wheeze at night
        \n\t-You can do all your usual activities and exercise freely
        \n\t-Most days you don’t need a reliever\n
        \nAny alterations in medication should be made in consultation with your personal physician
    </string>
    <string name="severity_moderate"><b>Your symptoms appear to be moderate</b>\n
        \nWe suggest stepping up your preventer medicine.
        \nUse your reliever as often as needed – through a spacer, if one can be used with your reliever inhaler.\n
        \n<b>Caution! Your asthma is getting worse when:</b>\n
        \n\t-You have symptoms most days (wheeze, tight chest, a cough or feeling breathless)
        \n\t-You are waking at night with symptoms
        \n\t-You are getting a cold
        \n\t-You feel short of breath when you exercise\n
        \nAny alterations in medication should be made in consultation with your personal physician
    </string>
    <string name="severity_severe"><b>Your symptoms appear to be severe</b>\n
        \nContinue your medicine for “getting worse”
        \nStart prednisone if you have it
        \n<b>Important: You need to see your doctor today</b>\n
        \n<b>Caution! Your asthma is getting severe when:</b>\n
        \n\t-Your symptoms are getting severe (wheeze, tight chest, a cough or feeling breathless)
        \n\t-Your reliever is only helping for 2‐3 hours, or you are using more than 12 puffs a day
        \n\t-You feel you need to see your doctor\n
        \nAny alterations in medication should be made in consultation with your personal physician
    </string>
    <string name="severity_emergency"><b>Let’s keep calm…</b>\n
        \n\t-Dial 111 for ambulance
        \n\t-Keep using your reliever as often as needed – through a spacer, if one can be used with your reliever inhaler
        \n\t-Even if you seem to get better seek medical help right away
        \n\t-If you haven’t started taking your prednisone, start now\n
        \n<b>Emergency:</b>\n
        \n\t-Your symptoms are getting more severe quickly
        \n\t-You are finding it hard to speak or breathe
        \n\t-Your reliever is not helping much
        \n\t-You are using your reliever every 1‐2 hours\n
        \nAny alterations in medication should be made in consultation with your personal physician
    </string>

    <!-- Record -->
    <string name="record_title">Your Medical Record</string>
    <string name="record_add">Add New Health Record</string>
    <string name="record_new">New Health Record</string>
    <string name="record_name_add">Add Record Title</string>
    <string name="record_name">Record Title:</string>
    <string name="record_details_add">Add Details</string>
    <string name="record_details">Details:</string>
    <string name="record_save">Save Health Record</string>

    <!-- Appointment -->
    <!-- Date/Time -->
    <string name="appointment_date_t">Date and Time</string>
    <string name="appointment_date_morning_t">Morning</string>
    <string name="appointment_date_morning_opt1">9AM - 10AM</string>
    <string name="appointment_date_morning_opt2">10AM - 11AM</string>
    <string name="appointment_date_morning_opt3">11AM - 12PM</string>
    <string name="appointment_date_afternoon_t">Afternoon</string>
    <string name="appointment_date_afternoon_opt1">1PM - 2PM</string>
    <string name="appointment_date_afternoon_opt2">2PM - 3PM</string>
    <string name="appointment_date_afternoon_opt3">3PM - 4PM</string>
    <!-- Output -->
    <string name="appointment_result_t">Your Reservation</string>
    <string name="appointment_result_s">Your Booking Details:</string>
    <string name="appointment_result_date">Date:</string>
    <string name="appointment_result_time">Time:</string>
    <string name="appointment_result_location">Location:</string>
    <string name="appointment_complete">Complete</string>

    <!-- Support -->
    <string name="support_choose">Choose a Service</string>
    <string name="support_blurb">Use our online chat to give instant medical advice, or use our hot-line to call our doctor direct</string>
    <string name="support_online_service_title">Online Service</string>
    <string name="support_online_service_write">Write a message</string>
    <string name="support_hotline_title">Hot-Line</string>
    <string name="support_hotline_calling">Calling&#8230;</string>
    <string name="support_hotline_dotor">Doctor</string>
    <string name="support_chat_bubble">Chat Bubble</string>
    <string name="title_activity_appointment_location">Map</string>

</resources>
